[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Fallopian tubes are part of this system in the human body.", "correct_answer": "Reproductive system", "incorrect_answers": ["Digestive system", "Urinary system", "Respiratory system"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a dog is wagging its tail, then it is safe to approach.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Erle Stanley Gardner created the great fictional lawyer Perry Mason. On which TV show did the lawyer Perry Mason practice law?", "correct_answer": "The Flintstones", "incorrect_answers": ["The Jetsons", "The Stanley Show", "The Brady Bunch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To eat this meal you would: wait for a fertilized egg until the 16th day of incubation, open it and swallow the fetus without removing anything from it except some feathers from your teeth.", "correct_answer": "Balut", "incorrect_answers": ["Dookers", "Nankotsu", "Mollejas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Quickly calculate 95^2 (i.e. 95X95). What is the result?", "correct_answer": "9025", "incorrect_answers": ["810025", "8125", "987,654,321"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carcino is a word of Greek origin which refers to the small intestines.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous beer brand uses the Clydesdale horse as its mascot?", "correct_answer": "Anheuser-Busch", "incorrect_answers": ["Fosters", "Upland", "Heineken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Slavic belief, what type of death caused the soul to become unclean and potentially transformed a corpse into a vampire?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Early death", "Violent death", "Death of an unbaptized person"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these words means biting, sarcastic, acid-mouthed?", "correct_answer": "Mordant", "incorrect_answers": ["Chthonic", "Quotidian", "Puerile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fine adjustment knob of the microscope is used to move the body tube when focusing the specimen under the low power objective.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Owen Wilson makes a cameo in the movie 3:10 to Yuma.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which river, flowing entirely through a single country or state, is the longest?", "correct_answer": "Vistula (Poland)", "incorrect_answers": ["Loire (France)", "Iowa (Iowa)", "Illinois (Illinois)"]}]